Music
Yes, please
What is your name?
My name is Kazuto Mokudai
What is the origin of your name?
My name is "Kazuto", which is written "peace" and "person".
I am a person of peace.
What do they call you?
Kazuto.
Mokkun.
Mocchan.
Where are you from?
Tokyo, Japan
Kazuto
What is your birthday?
May 20
What is your blood type?
AB
What is your favorite part of your face?
My whole face.
My hobby is fashion.
I am good at cooking.
Do something funny?
When I'm asked to do something funny.
I want to stop this restlessness.
I don't do it now.
What's your favorite food?
Nabe (hot pot).
Motsu nabe, kimchi nabe.
What is your least favorite food?
Dried plums.
What is your favorite color?
It's hard to choose, but I like gray.
I like gray.
My strength is that I like people. My strengths are that I like people.
I like talking to people.
I like talking to people and interacting with them.
I think that is my strength.
Disadvantages are
I'm the type of person who thinks
I'm the type of person who thinks for myself.
If I'm studying, I don't get it done.
I guess that's my disadvantage.
But I guess that's also a strength.
What's your favorite saying?
Um...
Charm point.
Appearance...
I've been told I'm mature.
But on the inside...
I think that's my charm point.
Is there anything about your personality that you want to fix?
Wow.
I'm a guy who lives in an interesting straight line.
I have my moments when I'm not sharp.
Sometimes it sticks and sometimes it doesn't.
I mean...
It's a little bit.
The funniest thing that happened to me recently.
That's me.
A member named Kosaku Koizumi.
Um...
Kosaku Koizumi is a good friend of mine.
He's a staging artist.
Mr. UG, who does our staging.
I called him "Mr. UG" even though he's always been a great help to me.
Because he's Brad, the clothes guy.
I laughed a little when I thought about it.
What's your latest topic?
Something that's been bothering me.
I've recently started going to the gym. I recently started going to the gym.
I'm trying to get in shape.
Muscle is the meat that becomes muscle.
but I didn't have the meat to become that muscle.
That's my problem.
First of all, I have to put on muscle.
My daily routine is
I wake up in the morning.
First thing I do is drink a lot of water.
Not just a little bit.
I drink a lot of water, not just a little bit.
If you could take only one thing on a deserted island, what would it be?
Kyung.
Like a Kyungpook set.
Camping gear.
A small ability. Like self-regeneration.
I'd like to have that resilience.
If you won the lottery, what would you spend it on?
I'd buy a building.
Yes, Bill.
How do you relieve stress?
I buy clothes... to relieve stress.
My treasures are... well... my friends and members.
I think it's something you can never get again. Relationships.
What's your earliest memory?
I think it's the first time my mother was angry with me.
I was carrying something and there was a handle on it.
I broke the handle a little bit.
I thought something was wrong, so I hid the handle.
When the mother saw that, she got angry.
I won't hide it!
Then I cried. I played air guitar.
The nicest guy at the scene is Jun Muto... who's the strictest.
Who's the strictest?
Our motto is "Freedom", so there might not be anyone strict.
A surprising side to you.
Me and Ryota Nakano.
Ryota also likes passion. Ryota likes Passion too.
I'm trying not to wear both of their brands.
Who is the most gorgeous face in Penjing?
Kaname
I guess Kaname.
What kind of a person is Kaname?
First of all, I want you to know that the cause is me.
First of all, I would like you to get to know me.
I'm not a cut-throat, but...
I'd like to cut my way in and out of things.
One secret about myself that the members don't know
When we were research students
When we were research students, we belonged to a research student unit called Battle Boys.
I have a Battle Boys T-shirt from that time.
They were costumes, so we weren't allowed to take them home.
I have one of those T-shirts at home.
I wonder if the staff from the research student days are in a hurry now.
I'm sorry. I have one.
I'm sorry.
I'll never let anyone beat me in this!
But you know what?
When you stand in front of the camera and take a shot like this...
I think I'm as good as him.
Who would you like to meet?
Takuya Kimura.
What's your personal boom? Sauna.
When I'm off duty, I'm outdoorsy. I eat lunch with friends, go shopping, and then go to the sauna.
He's a very active person.
What kind of kid were you?
I was kind of an adventurer. I was very inquisitive.
I liked to do athletic things that I'd never done before.
I liked going to places I'd never been before.
Who is your favorite comedian?
I really love...
Diane Tsuba.
I think she's really funny.
If the earth were to die tomorrow, what would you do?
I would look back at the pictures. I want to look back at the pictures.
I'd like to relive as many memories as possible.
If you could be reborn, what would you want to be?
I would like to be Kazuto Kida again.
Is that your kanji character?
I'm a person. Where would you like to travel to?
Hawaii I've always wanted to go to Hawaii.
I'd like to go to Hawaii, a place I've always dreamed of visiting.
I'd like to go to Hawaii, a place everyone says they'd like to visit.
I'd like to go to Hawaii and see what everyone is talking about.
Back muscles
Here's a question from the observers.
What is your favorite outfit?
My favorite outfit?
Well, I like that one the best... the one from the "Infinite Death" mv show, the black and white one, where everyone wears jackets... I like that one a lot.
What is your favorite onigiri?
Mentaiko (cod roe).
What I value is that I meet a lot of people through this activity.
Of course, I try my best to do interesting things, but I also value the way I interact with people.
What is your favorite phrase in your part?
What? Obviously, it's your fault.
I really liked the gymnastic festival.
If you were to give yourself a reward, what would it be?
Lately, a reward would be a nice meal.
Like going to a good yakiniku restaurant.
The choreography is my favorite part.
I can't wait to see what the members have to say about it!
It was the last song of the encore and the last song of the last song of the encore in the recent reversal of Ingaites.
I love the choreography because it really gives the audience a sense of the live performance of The Empathy.
What do you want to eat now?
Well, I'd like a cup of warm tea!
If I suddenly have 7 days free, I'll probably go to Kyoto.
After that, I'd like to spend some time in Fukuoka, and I'd like to travel from one place to another.
Sounds fun.
If seven people were a family, what would the family consist of?
Let's see... Kaname Yoshizawa, Mom, Takato Okura, Dad.
First son, Kosaku Koizumi Second son, Ryota Nakano Youngest son, Kazuto Kiuchi
Youngest sister, baby Masaya. Grandmother, Jun Muto. Baby sister Masaya Grandmother Jun Muto
I think it's a good line.
Where would you like to be in the classroom?
Next to the back of the room by the window.
I'm going to make a picture of the actors in the local section.
What's the reason?
A lot.
Free
They are a great group of people with a lot of personality and a lot of parts.
Thank you very much!
What if I were to compare the members to an oden club?
It's a lot of fun!
I like chikuwabu.
It's very chewy.
I can't stop sticking it in and sticking it in.
I like the long ones.
Next time, I usually crack one egg and go for one egg.
I enjoy it twice.
I have two sides.
Gap
Sugar-free and pure
I go for konjac!
Konnyaku is very hot!
But it's crunchy and tasty!
When konjac is big
When konjac is big, it goes with daikon radish.
Daikon soaks up a lot of moisture.
Take a breather.
Yoshizaka Nameko has a calm atmosphere.
Half a pen of konjac
Half a pen is soft!
It's so soft.
This is Koizumi Kosaku, isn't it?
And lastly
Mochi kinchaku as if to wrap the whole
This is Sakura-kun
If you could change your face, what color would it be?
I'd change it to green. No, just green.
What was your favorite picture book?
I liked "Rorori the Confrontation," didn't I?
What do you think is the appeal of the local club?
We were pretty intelligent.
We cook clothes and stuff.
We play difficult music.
But in reality...
I have a funny side and a cute side.
I think that's what makes him so appealing.
And also, each of them has their own good-looking power.
I guess that's the charm.
What kind of songs are fun to sing?
I have a song called "Run Away".
I like it so much that I listen to it in private.
Please describe your favorite emoji with your face.
Wow!
Smile.
I didn't need my fingers.
Today's breakfast was
Miso soup, rice balls...
And some kind of stir-fry.
What is the most relaxing and restful time for you?
I soak in the bathtub no matter how busy I am.
It gives me a break.
It's relaxing.
Rehearsals are a habit of mine.
It depends on the person.
I like to eat bread, rice balls and snacks that I can eat right away.
I go to rehearsals with a stock of ready-to-eat bread, rice balls and snacks.
I go to rehearsals with a stock of ready-to-eat bread, rice balls, and snacks.
What did you become?
But I want to create something.
I think I've always had a strong desire to imagine.
I think it's always been strong.
I think I've always had a strong desire to create something, to imagine something.
that would make life easier for everyone. I think I've been doing something entrepreneurial.
What episode has inspired you recently?
Kaname Yoshizawa went on a trip to Korea by himself.
I was surprised at his energy.
If you were an animal, what would you be?
I'm often called a frog.
I guess I'm like a frog.
But I like chiwaps, so I'd be a chiwap.
If you could switch places for a day, who would you be?
Well, I'd like to be a comedian.
If you had to perform outside of Japan, where would it be?
China, I guess.
I was in a Kamen Rider movie.
At that time, I received a lot of support from Chinese people.
I received a lot of support from people in China.
And there were people who came to see me.
I really want to do live performances.
Who do you respect?
Takuya Tomoda, of course.
I think his charm to attract people is really amazing.
I think it's really amazing.
What kind of movies do you want to see?
I've never seen the Marvel series.
Jun, one of our members, is a big fan of Marvel.
I saw a clipping of it the other day
I saw a clipping or something the other day and thought it looked really interesting.
I was wondering what movie I should watch first.
So...
I guess I'll start with the Marvel movies.
What should I look for when choosing clothes?
First of all
Does it look good on me?
And then...
Is it the size?
If anything, it's about being able to wear it in different ways.
Various expressions... Various expressions
I like to wear clothes that I think
I like clothes that can be styled in different ways.
What kind of bread do you buy at the bakery?
Fried bean-jam buns
Is it an appealing point?
I don't have an appeal point.
I think you can see the number of different types of wood.
I'm sure you can see the number of different kinds of wood.
I guess the appeal point is that the fall never comes.
What are three things you wish you had this week?
The timing of the deliveries and
My schedule was great!
When I went to the convenience store
I bought a lot of things at the convenience store.
I bought a bunch of stuff at the convenience store.
I think it was this morning.
When I woke up.
It's great to wake up, isn't it?
The source of my energy.
It was when I updated my Instagram.
I received comments from observers and
That's what we do.
like this
as a source of sustenance
I'm doing my best.
What is your favorite side dish?
I'm a picky eater.
I really like simple dishes like gingerbread.
Speaking of yourself
Candles...
It's very close to the music I usually listen to.
I also want to be a man who fits the atmosphere of a candle
I also want to be a man who fits the atmosphere of a candle.
In a previous life?
I think I was a prince.
Last supper?
Well... it's a classic. Well, I know it's the royal way, but...
I think it's the food your mother makes.
Which seat on the bullet train do you like?
I like the window side.
I think it's nice to be able to draw a good picture when I sleep.
Where do you want to go most now?
Oh, yes!
I heard that it's a mystery why the pyramids were built.
No, that's why I want to see it.
I wonder what the mystery is.
There are many theories.
Hey, you guys who won't close the channel!
They say it's very heavy.
Even a single stone is heavy.
What's the latest foreign word you learned?
Wow!
I've been studying.
What?
What's that in the textbook?
What's the last foreign word you learned?
Um...
Let's see...
In Korean, it's like...
I heard it's used as a signal.
Next time I'm called...
I was thinking that I want to say "Hey!
the next time I'm called
I learned it.
My right hand
Right next to me.
Za-right-me-ka
Za-right-me-ka.
The right side of the eye
the right eye
Za-right-me-ka
I don't know if I'm right or wrong.
I don't know if it's a za-right eye or not.
I don't know if it's my "za-right eye" or my "za-right eye". It is the most important thing to be grateful.
It's the best thing you can do.
Show us some of your favorite photos you've taken recently.
This one right here.
I was on location for the first time.
I was on location for the first time, and I got to interact with a dog.
That's the one I took.
I had a great time, and I can't wait to go back.
When I feel happy in winter
I love Christmas.
I feel happy when I see the town is bustling with people.
Winter is the best!
The four letter job that comes to mind
The four-letter job is
Oh, yeah!
Yaaaaaah!
Seino
Denko Ishibari
Electro-acoustic fire
What sport are you good at?
Tennis. Sort tennis.
What is the most memorable dream you had while sleeping?
I opened my eyes and found myself in a sea turtle.
It was terrifying.
What was your dream when you were little?
Wow, when you were little, do you really mean your very first dream?
I wanted to be a racer.
Coffee drinker or tea drinker? Tea?
Uh, tea.
Sorry about the coffee.
It's still a little bitter for my palate.
I drink a lot of straight tea.
What's your favorite doughnut?
Uh...
I'd have to say Angel French.
Especially cabbage rolls.
Oh, what do you want to try most right now?Oh, the things I want to challenge myself the most right now
Oh, mountain climbing.
I want to climb a mountain!
What song in the local language would you like to listen to the most?
It's a little bit calm.
A little bit calm, a little bit quiet, a little bit fresh.
I'd like you to listen to this kind of music.
I really want everyone to listen to it now.
What do you want to do this year?
Present clothes to my juniors.
I have a lot of clothes in my closet.
But you know what?
I don't have any juniors that I'm close with.
I mean...
This is a serious matter.
One last thing.
Oh, one last thing.
Thank you for taking the time to look at 100 questions.
I hope you learned a lot about wood furniture.
I really wish I could ask you all 100 questions, so I can be closer to you.
So let's keep working together to be closer to each other.
I hope we can continue to work together in the future.
Thank you for watching.
Thank you very much.